♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals
♪ Are caught in an endless chase
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl
♪ An evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse
♪ And in a rocket
ship she hunts him
♪ All across the universe
I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And I'll monitor his mind
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
Robot roll call.
- Cambot.
- You're on.
- Gypsy.
- Oh my stars.
- Tom Servo.
- Check me out.
- Crow.
- I’m different.
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-la-la
♪ Just repeat to
yourself, it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
Help!
Crow, what is it?
Hey Mike, give me
a hand here will you?
I'm having a real problem
with my Thighmaster.
Probably should have
looked at the directions
before I started
messing with it, but no,
I just had to work
on my trouble spots.
Hey Crow, did you know
this was a Thaw Master?
What? A Thaw Master?
Well, how do you like
that? (laughs falsely)
Hi Mike, hi Crow.
Say guys, breakfast is
going to be a little late.
This pot roast just
won't thaw yet.
There's something wrong
with the Thaw Master.
No Servo, this
is a Thighmaster.
(laughs) A Thighmaster?
Well, no wonder.
(all laugh sarcastically)
This is never going to thaw.
We'll be right back.
- Son of a gun.
- That's good.
(light music)
(laughs) Thaw
Master, Thighmaster.
Thighmaster, Thaw Master.
Reminds me of that
time I tried to wear
that hand hammered
wok for underpants.
Yeah, that really...
Hey, Mrs.. Forrester's calling.
We'll begin
with a frontal cut.
- But has he been washed?
- I washed him earlier.
With my mind.
It was not pleasant.
Hi, guys. Things have
deteriorated down here.
Unless I'm mistaken,
and frankly,
what are the odds of that?
The brain guys are
about to dissect Bobo.
Say, could we get on
with this dissection?
- I think it's almost mealtime.
- Bobo's very stupid.
Anyway, I'm locked in
some kind of force-field.
(electronic sounds)
So here's the deal.
I know you guys despise
me, even loathe me.
So could you help me out?
Careful. Careful.
I need a distraction
of some kind.
If you can think of something,
I promise to never show you
another bad movie again.
Really.
Never again, ever.
Hmm, you think
we can trust her?
I don't know.
(pleadingly) Pwease?
Pwease, pwetty
pwease, for Pearl?
Pearl needs a distraction
so bad. Pwease?
Come on. For Pearl.
Pwease?
(Crow retches)
My god, stop it.
Okay, fine, fine.
Just don't do that.
Maybe the nanites have an idea.
Hello nanites, could you
create a distraction?
A distraction? Cool.
I know, I know, I know.
We can send a fleet of tiny
ships down there to pants them.
(nanite laughs)
Well, gee, that seems
- kind of complicated.
- Oh, I know.
Simpler. Sure, okay.
I know, we could always
biosynthesize an android
and send down there to say,
"Hey, look over there."
(nanite laughs)
(Mike laughs falsely) Great.
Why don't you just
cut the tractor beam
that's holding us here?
Ah, fine, a
number three, sure.
We never get to
do anything fun.
(pulsing)
There. It's done.
Whoa. Hey, great.
How's that, Mrs. Forrester?
Is that distracting?
- What the devil was that?
- Very distracting.
- Yes.
- Observer, you remain here.
And I will check it out.
- Certainly.
- Guard.
Hey, guard. I got
a sick man in here.
Do you mean me?
Because I'm not sick.
- I’m being dissected.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
- Your friend Observer
created an invisible
man with his mind
and put him in here with me.
I suppose that's possible--
Yeah, and now he's
looking real sick.
Uh-oh, you better
get in here quick.
I don't think you'd
want him to die.
Well, where is here?
He's right over there. Look.
Oh boy, he sure looks bad.
I'm sorry. I'm just not--
Okay, beautiful,
you and your brain
are coming with me, Mister.
Oh, don't hurt
my brain, please.
Everything's nice
and comfortable.
Everybody's okay.
(Observer winces)
Just keep coming with me.
Come on Bobo, we're
getting off this planet.
Wouldn't it be
more polite to wait
- until after I'm dissected?
- Shut up!
- Okay.
- You put down that thing!
I'm not putting down that!
(all shout at once)
Mike, I accidentally lied.
Your movie today
is She Creature.
I'm not putting down the thing!
Just watch me!
(all shout at once)
She Creature? (scoffs)
You know who I'm thinking
is a she creature? Huh?
- Yeah?
- Huh?
Yeah?
Hey, I tried to steer
us away from the planet,
but the stupid smart guys have
cut our navigational system.
Well, maybe the
nanites can take care
- of that little problem, huh?
- Yeah.
We'll fix your little
problem for you, uh-huh.
Hey Steve, Mr. Nelson
wants a number seven, pronto.
Well there you
go, that took care...
Hey, what's a
number seven anyway?
(explosion)
(all shout)
Mike, you blew
up another planet.
What is your deal?
I just told them to take
care of a little problem.
And they did.
"Here comes Mike.
Destroyer of worlds."
Oh god of fire and
vengeance. Stay away from me.
Get away from me.
(buzzer)
We got movie sign.
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
- Planet killer.
- I didn't. It's not me.
This is as colorful as
the movie's going to get.
Ah, The RuPaul Story.
(1950s horror film music)
Hey, Tim Conway as Dorf
is going to be in this.
Hey, there's Tim Finn.
There's Gil Hodges.
There's Gil Gerard.
There goes Joe Pesci.
There's Prunella Scales.
There's Abe Vigoda.
Is there a sturgeon
in the house?
Can I borrow a fin?
- Sea turtle.
- Yes, I do (laughs)
"Based on drunken comments
"made one night by Lou Rusoff."
At least the
production was supervised.
Things didn't get out of hand.
Clearly the ocean does
not have metered ramps.
"Oh, it's humid today. Oof."
(lightning sound effect)
Lee Trevino goes fishing.
(scoffs) Samuel Z. Dunkoff.
Yeah, Samuel Z. Wienerhead.
Well, I think ideally it
should be related to his name.
Oh.
Hey, there's Bennett
Cerf, and Billy Ocean!
Stop it, Servo.
Once again folks, a
Golden State Production.
Is this a
Show-Me-State Production?
No, I think it's a
Golden State Production.
Wait a minute, wasn't it
already produced by someone?
Edward Cahn, Edward
Cahn, let me rock it.
That's all I wanna do.
Edward Cahn, let me rock you.
That's all I want to do.
Gidget meets Magritte.
Now, on this very
night, I have called out
from the unknown
depths of time itself.
- Uh-huh, and you are?
- And she is here.
And with her coming, the
world will never be as it was.
Neither man nor animal
will be the same.
Nor manimal.
This, I, Dr. Carlo Lombardi,
have brought into being.
Dr. Carlo Lombardi of Yonkers.
(dog barks)
And I, Dr. Woof Woof Lombardi.
Well, I can certainly
see how, sleep!
"I need my worm
medicine. I need it now."
"What's that? Grandpa
Lombardi fell down a well?"
"I'm sorry, Mr. Lombardi.
"I mistook you for someone else.
"I know my family
owes you a lot."
"Look, you smell like spam.
"It was my mistake, my mistake."
"God, I hate cats."
"I left a present for you
in the front seat of your car."
"Top breeder, Bat Masterson."
Hmm, Howard
the Duck was here.
"I've got sand in my Derby."
(flatly) "Hey,
hey, I'm the Monkee.
"People say I monkey around."
(faux laughs) Fun times
at the Kennedy compound.
"Here you go,
Mr. Trafficante."
Enjoying your weekend
with the idle rich?
"When does it start?"
Pretty heady stuff for a
professor of psychic research.
You sound a
little disapproving.
Not at all.
I just don't feel
I belong in a world
of yachts and racing stakes.
What the?
Hello?
Including your father.
Kind of frightens me.
Oh come now,
this type of life
shouldn't be too
hard to get used to.
Let's face it.
I'm an Alloway farm boy
with a professorship
at the university.
But basically, a farm boy.
I don't belong in all that.
Very well, then.
We'll get you away
from them for a while.
A walk along the ocean'll do it.
- I’d like that.
- “But I don't know how."
I don't know how your
fiance will react to that idea.
Oh, Bob, my ex-fiance?
That makes quite a difference.
- Come on, Ted.
- “You've got the backstory.
"Now run!"
"I'm ready for
some football."
(mumbles in plummy accent)
Oh, mafia goons
and withered spinsters
- partying together.
- So that horrid blond
- finally let you go, eh?
- “Hey, that's our daughter."
That horrid blond represents
an investment portfolio
of half a million bucks.
Where's Dorothy?
She went for a walk with Ted.
- Oh, I wish she hadn't.
- Why?
Dr. Lombardi said
something terrible
is going to happen along this
part of the coast tonight.
Some visitation from
the occult world.
Oh, the occult world?
Oh no, really, seriously.
You must meet him.
He's wonderful.
Some women keep beds
or grow roses for kicks.
My wife supports
crack occultism.
A couple of years ago it was
that spiritualistic medium.
Last year, swarmy
something or other,
and now Dr. Lombardi.
- “Oh, Professor Firefly."
- So long as it amuses you.
No, seriously.
He puts this girl
into a deep trance.
And takes her back 300 years.
Now, she tells about
her life in England.
I tell you, it's uncanny.
(quietly) Yeah, yeah.
"I married Aunt Bee."
Looks pretty serious
between Dorothy and Ted.
She's falling for him.
I'm afraid it's
pretty one-sided so far.
Nonsense. If she wants
him, she'll get him.
What's the market price on
professors of psychic research?
Not very high, I imagine.
- (laughs) You goose.
- “You pheasant."
Mother's a little
disappointed in you.
She thought you'd
liven up the party
with some of the
tricks of your trade.
- “Nope."
- You know, hypnotism.
Demonstrations of
thought transference.
I know.
She thought I'd make it
an age regression party.
I told her that was Dr.
Lombardi's field, not mine.
"I could use a Frogurt."
(menacing music)
The Fleet Street
line of beachwear.
"Is this the
Mr. Kite everyone's
"always doing stuff
for the benefit of?"
Paladin's beach home.
"Smithy, Merv, you maniacs."
Oh, it's Helen Keller's room.
"Hello, wall."
"Make yourself at home.
"Just looking at the wall here."
"Uh, guys, are we still
going to watch the game?"
"Damn cats."
"This is scary.
"I'm not going to get any
(shouts) sleep tonight."
"Man with flaming
swim fins did this."
"Mayhem I can put up with.
It's the damn dust I just..."
(dog barks)
"Rin Tin Tin in Coming Home."
(whispers) "Hey, do you
know where my socks are?"
The death of Tyne Daly.
He's an amazing man.
Do you know him?
Quite well.
He's challenged me
publicly and privately
to disprove the authenticity
of his experiments.
"And to oil
jockstrap wrestling."
(dog barks)
That sounds like King's bark.
Since it's King
running right at us,
- you're probably right.
- Yeah.
(dramatic music)
"I can't believe I
ate the whole thing."
"As your RA, I should warn
you you're facing expulsion."
"I'm going out for a
sack of White Castles.
"You want anything?"
(dog barks)
"I just found out
my food is mostly rice.
"Can I have some lamb please?"
Well what's the
matter with him?
Maybe he's jealous of me.
Oh, that's weird.
You haven't given
him cause to be, yet.
(dog barks)
"I think I've made my point."
He wants us to follow him.
"Oh, gee, do you think so?
"Of course I want
you to follow me."
"Well, I think I'll
grab the Boogie Board
- “and hit some waves."
- I hope to god
we don't see this guy in a thong
- before the movie's over.
- Ugh.
(dog barks)
"I'm going to tell Hobie
to stay away from the pier."
That looked like
Dr. Lombardi to me.
It was Dr. Lombardi.
"And that sounds
like King's bark."
"Now come here.
"I want to prove to you,
I'm not the only one
"who craps in the corner."
(dog barks)
"Huh, what's that boy?
"A four-year
assumable mortgage?"
"Let's go."
"I think I must
have killed some people
"and I'm feeling a
little bad about it."
"Should I wait here, or..."
♪ Everybody is a starfish
"Shazam, my pipe's gone."
The Dallas Cowboys
training camp.
"King, what
have you done here?
"King, kill outside.
Outside, King!"
"You're gonna
hang for this, King."
Well, what is it?
Go on home and
call the police.
The police?
I'll wait here
for them. Hurry up.
"King is the Scorpio Killer."
The only movie
based on a lens flare.
- “Huh, I don't feel fresh."
- Okay.
(light music)
Never seen anything like it.
Neck's broken in two like
a pile-driver hit her.
- The man's too.
- “I suspect a pile-driver."
- I’ve got $600 here.
- “That's 300 each."
- That lets robbery out.
- Hey.
Here's something.
Of course you can
say that about anything.
A piece of seaweed.
All the way to the door.
"Eisenhower, P.I."
The carpet's wet here.
Might be a footprint.
Go into the kitchen and see if
there's any flour, will you?
"Roll in it and
pan fry yourself."
You willing to
swear you saw Lombardi
coming out of this house?
Course.
"Who wants cookies? I'm
going to make some Toll House."
"By the way, why
do we do this, Earl?"
Detective's
handbook number one.
Chuck flour and blow on it.
What'd make a
footprint like that?
Bill Walton?
Clever man could
have forged it.
Do you think a human
could have done this?
"No, I think a
mudskipper did it."
Oh, I almost forgot
about your firm belief
in Lombardi's black
magic and occult powers.
It's not me. It's my
wife. She swears by him.
What did he say was
coming to roam among us?
"He said (shouts) 'Sleep.' "
The first life-form
of someone living today.
Over a million years old.
Strom Thurmond?
You see, doctor, that's
how civilized we are.
Scratch the veneer
and what do you find?
A whole car-load
of superstitions
waiting to be catered to.
Vampires, witchcraft,
supernatural creatures.
Being brought back
from the past.
"Just patting my own
arm. I'm not in this scene."
He's got a lot of
people listening to him.
It's not me. It's my wife.
All right. It's your wife.
"Yeah, like somebody
lays with you anyway."
You willing to
identify Lombardi now?
Make things a lot simpler.
Sure.
You wait here
for the lab boys.
And I want pictures.
Plenty of them.
You gonna leave
me alone here?
It's not like it was
an ordinary stiff.
I can take that
seven days a week.
Come on.
But, it might come back.
But it's not you
that is superstitious.
It's your wife who's
the gullible one.
"I'm a flaky
little detective elf."
(bustling crowd)
"Brooklyn, California."
"Get your bags of rat filth."
"Step right up. I'll touch
you for a quarter. Come on."
"Rat filth."
"Hey, I found
another dirty diaper."
We'll make you, break you,
set you on a farm out West.
10 cents. Yes, siree.
Hello, Lombardi.
Lousy night. No business at all.
I find it very pleasant.
I heard a scream from your
place about 15 minutes ago.
I thought it was Andrea.
I ran over to check up,
see if she was in trouble.
I told you to
keep away from there.
I knew her long
before you did, doc.
I knew her when she was
a carnival follower.
Every time we hit a town
she'd be there waiting for us.
So she's a carnival preceder.
I've asked you
to forget that.
"Have we met?"
Well, anyway, I heard
the screams, so I went over.
The back door was
open, I went in.
She was out cold.
How do you keep her
under like that?
I thought she was dead. I
was going to call the cops.
It's so tiresome
having to warn you
to mind your own business.
So very tiresome.
Well, I'm naturally curious.
Poor kid, she was out cold.
What's it all about, doc?
Why do you keep her
under like that?
"Alfie."
I have an idea
you'll find out soon.
"Was it something I said
at breakfast this morning?"
"See his lecture series.
"Let a smile be
his calling card."
"Author, lecturer,
choreographer."
"Endorsed by King the dog."
"I barked my ass off.
"You'll laugh, you'll
growl, you'll pee."
"See him perform live with
his band, Thunkersaurus."
"Damn, I left the
woman plugged in."
(menacing music)
This guy leaves grease
stains in the air as he walks.
"I come home from
a hard day of skulking
"and the place isn't cleaned?
"You're just laying there
thinking of bonbons."
You're in a
deep sleep, Andrea.
A very deep sleep.
"I was."
I’ll touch you,
and slowly you will wake.
"And you'll get
me some damn dinner."
(they mime slurpy kiss)
"Well, I'd better
repaint my head."
"Someone ripped off
our lawn gnome again."
- Hmm?
- What the?
Yeah, she's dreaming of
old carnivals she's been to.
"There any turkey
sausages left?"
♪ There'll be creatures over
♪ The white cliffs of Dover
"Well, I got to go bleed
the sprinklers, I don't know."
"Oh honey, please don't
spend another Christmas
"passed out on the couch."
Now you'll come
back to me, Andrea.
You'll feel refreshed.
You'll remember nothing.
“You’ll remember
how to go potty
"and chew and stuff, but..."
He's like an
unattractive Slim Whitman.
"That's great, Mesmer,
but you left jelly
"all over the cutting
board this morning."
"I've got to go levitate
over to Denny's for my shift."
What time is it?
Shortly after midnight.
Don't let it all
hang down, please.
You've had me
in a deep hypnosis
for more than an hour.
I asked you not to do that.
Well, you were tired.
You needed the rest.
(Servo mimes kiss)
I need to get away from here.
Away from you.
"Uh, can I come?"
I hate this place.
I hate the sound of the ocean.
I hate you.
"I can't help but feel
that was directed at me."
"I didn't mean I
hate you in a bad way."
"Anyone call
about the charger?"
You'll never leave me.
You can't.
I will.
Someday I will.
Soon.
"You want to
make some nachos?"
As long as I'm
alive I'll possess you.
"I should bag those leaves."
There's something
beyond yourself
that makes you need me.
You've taken my
soul away from me.
"You told me to take it
so you wouldn't overuse it."
(knock on door)
The door is open. Come in.
"Can we get two
seats together?"
"Hi, Max."
"May I suggest a
size up from that?"
- Yeah.
- I’m Lieutenant James.
Hello.
"This is Timmy."
- Dr. Erickson?
- “Umm, breast?"
Uh, yeah?
Is this the man
you saw coming out of
- the Jefferson house?
- “Boobies, exactly."
- Yeah.
- No doubt in your mind?
No.
He knows me quite well.
I've been trying to interest
him in my work for some time.
You don't deny you were
in the Jefferson house
approximately 15
minutes after 11?
Not at all.
Well, that closes
the investigation.
I won't need you any
longer, doctor. Thank you.
Nor you, miss.
Wow, it's the federal
witness seduction program.
"Umm, 'Sleep?' "
" 'Sleep?' "
"You want to
go home and play?
- “I got a box of men."
- What's it all about?
Maybe we can talk about
it over a cup of coffee.
I'd like that.
"Would you like a C-cup
or a D-cup of coffee?"
"So, you go to
carnival locations
"and wait for them, huh?"
(mystical music)
- Ooh.
- Hey.
"Look into my oily T-zone."
I can't go with you.
"I'm not a coffee achiever."
And he ducks
out of the screen.
(Servo laughs)
Bye.
"Guess the stain
and win a prize."
Oh.
You say you
knew they were dead
the minute you
saw the open door.
- “Yeah, see?"
- Yes, pity.
Nice young couple.
She came out of the ocean,
just as I said she would.
And she'll come again.
Look, I'm not
a paying customer.
I'm a police officer.
She comes from the
beginning of time.
(they fake coughing)
Huge and indestructible.
"Thank you."
And I'm the force
that gives her life.
All I know, you were seen
coming out of that house
leaving two corpses behind you.
And the occult world
notwithstanding,
I think I'll take you downtown
and wait until the
reports come in.
I can tell you what
the reports will say.
"They'll say
(shouts) 'Sleep.' "
That no living
thing killed them.
Yeah, I know.
It was a materialization
of the prehistoric female.
A transmigration of the
soul of a living woman,
into her first life body.
Save it, save
it for downtown.
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
Hey Mike, there you are.
I had an idea and I
wanted to run it by
a totally average,
unspectacular,
not overly-bright
consumer, and here you are.
(faux laughter)
Yeah, sure Crow.
Good. Hey, give me that
thing under there will you?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
It's my Tickle Me
Carlo Lombardi doll.
Oh, wow. What the?
Yeah, it's just like the
lovable Tickle Me Elmo doll.
- Only it's Carlo Lombardi.
- What? Why?
Oh that's a lot
of little boys,
and it's a reaction to dolls,
but you'll grow to
love it as you take it
into your room, perhaps prop it
next to your bed as you sleep.
He'll watch over you.
He's Dr. Carlo Lombardi.
- Crow, why you make a doll?
- Go ahead, Mike. Tickle him.
No.
Oh, I think
you'd better, Mike.
Tickle Me Carlo Lombardi
doesn't like to be disappointed.
Well, just to be safe, okay.
That's right.
(dolls laughs)
Tickle Me Carlo Lombardi
is your friend.
Forever.
(doll laughs)
Yeah, and I made him sticky
so he's even more fun.
(Mike strains)
You can feed him
the special baby food
included and in a few minutes
change Tickle Me Carlo
Lombardi's daidie.
No, no!
And there's a song too.
♪ Who's that fat little
funny little doll
♪ It's Tickle Me Carlo Lombardi
♪ Who's little diaper
needs a good little change
♪ It's Tickle Me
Carlo Lombardi
Tickle Me Carlo Lombardi
and Tickle Me Carlo
Lombardi sold separately.
(doll laughs)
You know, that thing's
kind of creepy.
No, I don't think it'll work.
You can have that
doll though, Mike.
I'm done with it. Thank you.
(doll laughs)
(light music)
Huh, will you look at that?
Despite all his money,
Mr. Drysdale eats alone.
"Where's my shirred eggs?"
(dog barks)
"Works every time."
That dog, it
gives me the jitters.
I get a nervous Adam's apple,
and that makes my tie unfold.
Inspired by Balki.
- Morning, gentlemen.
- Morning, Ted.
Dorothy will be
down in a minute.
"Dorothy can't.
I killed her."
I'm certainly not too popular
with that member of your family.
Take him to the
kitchen and get him
- something to eat, huh?
- The last time I took him
to the kitchen, he
nearly had the cook.
"Thank you very
much. Was so stupid."
Come on, dog.
(dog growls and barks)
"Oh god, I am dead.
My carotid artery."
"Racket's really
heavy today."
Carnelli arrives at 10.
Good. Makes your
men get up early.
Shows he's aggressive,
wants to get ahead.
"Damn Jerries at it again."
You give me too much
credit, Mr. Chappel.
This Jefferson thing
last night, pretty grim.
Kept them all
buzzing for a while
- after Dorothy came home.
- “I’m over here, sir."
It's surprising
how many of them
think that Lombardi had
something to do with it.
The whole gang's been
down to see his show.
- “Sorry, looked at you."
- Chappel tried to bully me
- into going along.
- “Damn wigwags."
Take a look at
that front page.
"God ailing, still holds on."
"Let me get my
welding glasses on here."
I play a little
game every morning.
- I call it my front page game.
- “Sure you do."
I'm getting a little old
to play most of the others.
"I'm a limp noodle."
I read the front
page every morning
and see if I can pick
out an item or two
that will make me
a lot of money.
Surprising how often
it's worked out.
You ever try it?
No, I can't say I have.
Can the She Creature
begin killing now?
You read about
the Jefferson murder?
Yes.
There's a million
dollar idea in that.
Last paragraph. Read it.
"Sell something for
a million dollars."
"One baffling
aspect of the case
"concerns Dr. Carlo Lombardi,
"carnival hypnotist
and prognosticator."
- That's the plot summary.
- “Only last week,
"he predicted that such a
murder would take place,
"describing it with
grizzly accuracy.
"He was questioned by the
police, but not held."
"Molly Ivins can't say that."
You see a fortune in that?
- Yes.
- “Oh, wait. No."
Yes, and it's
right up your alley.
Ouch.
And yours is a
wedding present.
You're serious, aren't you?
Couldn't be more so.
We'll take this two-bit
local sideshow man
and build him into the
biggest thing in the country.
Build him up until his
name's on everyone's lips.
Lombardi books.
Syndicated columns,
lectures, television shows.
"Cheese, a line
of underwear."
This prediction of his
is worth a million dollars
- and you and I can do it.
- Where do I fit in?
"You don't. I bought
you out already."
You can give him the
stamp of authenticity.
(Crow mimics his accent)
"Dr. Erickson,
"psychic research
specialist says
"Lombardi experiments amazing.
"Open new avenues in
the understanding of
the subconscious."
Why don't you kiss him
instead of talking him to death?
They'll swallow it, and
they'll swallow it whole
- and love it.
- “Yes."
This is the sort of escape
stuff the world's crying for.
Look at my wife and her friends.
- “No thanks."
- It’s a natural.
It'll be a lot for me,
and money for you and Dorothy.
I've been trained to fight
stupidity and ignorance,
- not get rich on it.
- “So put 'em up!"
A man like Lombardi put
hypnosis back 25 years.
"Ever prune your ferns?"
They've taken a
modern tool of science
and made a plaything out of it.
Worse than that, a weapon,
and in the hands of
quacks like Lombardi...
- Quack.
- A dangerous weapon.
And you want me to help
sell him to the public?
"I'm going to kick your ass."
Wait until that
loot starts rolling in.
That'll take care
of your scruples.
I'll go and talk
to him tomorrow.
- What do you say?
- Forget it!
"So, we're on."
I don't need
that kind of money.
"I need wampum bucks."
(crowd murmur)
(flatly) Do you
wanna go faster?
Raise your hand if...
Yes, sirree, try
your luck. 10 cents.
- One tenth of a dollar.
- Where's Lombardi's place?
Right next door,
but he's closed.
Been having trouble
with the police.
Yeah, I read about
it in the papers.
You want to get in, just
jingle a couple of coins.
The doors open automatically.
His kissing booth isn't
doing very well is it?
"See Carlo Lombardi's
erotic Dance of the Veils."
"Hello, (shouts) sleep."
I've been expecting you.
How in the devil did you
know I was traveling?
What do you mean you
were expecting me?
I was communicating
with your thoughts
before you left your home.
"Yeah, communicate
with my butt."
Communicating with
my thoughts, huh?
I suppose you can tell me
what I'm doing here too.
"You're talking to me."
You've come down here
to discuss a business
matter with me.
Good guess, Lombardi.
- Remarkable guess.
- I’m a remarkable man.
"Uh, right?"
Won't you come
in, Mr. Chappel?
Kind of an odd
bed and breakfast.
Let's get to the point.
How would you like
to be a rich man
- as well as a remarkable one?
- “Hello."
- Naturally.
- Enough to get you
out of this crazy place.
You have got something to sell.
How can you expect to
get your price in here?
The Facts about
Reincarnation, 35 cents.
I'll get you 3.50 for that.
I'd be most grateful, sir--
Yes, we'll make them pay
real money to see your act.
- I have no act.
- “Yeah, I saw it."
I have knowledge.
(Chappel laughs knowingly)
That's the boy,
that's the boy.
Keep a straight face
and hit 'em hard.
Lord Knute Rockne.
I'm a businessman, Lombardi.
I can see money in
this. Big money.
"Big Bellamy's wheel money."
50/50, what do you say?
- I’m overwhelmed.
- Okay.
Our deal starts as of now.
Come over to my
house tomorrow night.
I'm having some
people come over.
It might do us some good.
Newspaperman, a book publisher.
A doctor of psychic
research, a Dr. Erickson.
"Yeah, John and
Yoko will stop by."
Yes, I know him.
One of my most
outspoken critics.
Mm-hmm.
Get him involved too if you can,
even if it's only
to call you crazy.
Make good publicity. That's
what we need. Publicity.
And play it up big.
Give them everything you've got.
Some more of this
She Creature stuff.
Some more predictions.
Murder next month maybe.
Unfortunately it may
happen sooner than that.
- Very much sooner.
- “Wait, is this the 20th?"
I feel her presence even now.
No presents before Christmas.
She'll come out
of the ocean tonight.
That's the stuff.
That's the stuff, the big lie.
That's what sells.
I'll see you tomorrow night,
and remember, play it up big.
- Big nasally Ninereeds.
- We've got to shake them.
We'll shake them.
See you tomorrow night.
"Try the pronto
pups by the way."
♪ To the good life
"Hmm, pigeon kidneys
turned out runny again."
Bob Dornan
after the election.
(menacing music)
"You sleeping? Karen
called about bridge club."
You will go into
a much deeper sleep.
Ugh.
Very deep.
"Like moodies deep,
man, really deep."
You will go back in time.
"You will find
neck wattles sexy."
I command you.
"Did you have
the Cobb salad?"
Leave your body.
"You can always
pick it up later."
This is simply hypnotic
suggestion, you understand.
He's not insisting on
anything. Suggestion.
"Oh, damn Bumpus's
dog, get off the lawn!"
(Servo belches)
"Oh, excuse me."
The ocean needs Zantac.
"No catch, no
catch, out of bounds."
Samurai lobster.
"Why do they have to
park in front of our house?"
"A knife who knew
me as Jacob Marley."
"Oh, it's just the stairs
that bother me now, dear."
Oh, the Hendersons
got a new big screen.
"I'm the special tonight.
"You can have me
with drawn butter,
"relish tray,
fruit cup or gravy,
"sliced tomato salad or muffin."
Okay, tough one.
Who's uglier here?
"Carlo Lombardi for Acuvue."
You know, the same
features rearranged
could be very attractive.
"You will obey, oh, look at
"the Henderson tramp out there."
"That Mickey Spillane
sure can write."
"Apartment 12, okay."
Who's that?
(creature growls)
"Just lettin’ the
neighborhood know about
"the new Red Lobster."
"Oh, I forgot. Let
me, quick, get ready."
"From Doctor Carlo Lombardi,
"a singing death-o-gram."
"Get back.
(shouts) "Back!"
(Johnny shouts)
Oh, ooh.
Death by Murphy Bed.
They killed Sauvage Pierre.
(light music)
"Hmm, hmm, I photograph
beautifully, yes."
- Oh, hello, lieutenant.
- “Hello, Max."
Lombardi.
- You killed Johnny.
- Oh, did I?
Well, prove that and I'll
have to face a murder charge.
Can you prove you were
in here when it happened?
I can.
But I don't see what
difference it makes.
I warned you she'd come again.
And you laughed at me.
Not as hard as you're
laughing at me right now.
(Mike laughs falsely)
I'm gonna book you.
On what charge?
For being in
communication with a world
that you say doesn't exist?
You're a murderer
and I'm gonna prove it.
"But first a purple Herman."
Lieutenant, I urge you
to keep the beaches clear.
It's my civic
duty. Take it easy.
"This is from
Men's Wearhouse."
"No Barbara Hershey/Bette
Midler vehicles."
(police sirens)
"All sand must go."
Yeah, a little kid
pooped in the ocean.
They had to close
the whole thing.
Eww.
What's Chappel's
interest in this maniac?
I wouldn't know.
I'm only his lawyer.
Maybe he just hates
to see injustice done.
(Servo coughs)
I'll bet.
Maybe it's because Lombardi
is entertaining at
his house tonight.
"Are you going with anyone?
"Oh, ooh."
- Doctor, are you all right?
- Yes.
The next time
this man is pulled in
on some trumped-up charge,
we'll sue for false arrest.
"Or, we don't have to."
Most interesting experience.
I'm quite certain I
made a few new converts.
(flatly) "Come
back, come back.
"Uh, nothing."
Heimi's pissed.
(piano plays uptempo)
"Honey, this
is supposed to be
"a memorial service
for grandpa."
Cha-cha-cha.
Cha, cha?
"And she's only seven."
Keyser Soze on piano.
Since when have you got
into that spook stuff, Chappel?
There must be money in it.
No, no, no.
You've got me wrong.
Quite sensational.
Genuine thing.
He's made a convert out of me.
Now I know
there's a buck in it.
(robots laugh in posh voices)
I'm so excited.
Doctor Lombardi, here
in my very own home.
- (posh voice) "Oh!"
- And I thought it was
- going to be a boring weekend.
- If what you say is true
I'm certainly going to drop
the alley bin olly group.
They're becoming quite ordinary.
Just about anyone can join.
Yeah, it's funnyman Levsotop.
There he goes.
You're a dumb
square-head like this guy,
aren't you, Mike?
Actually, that's
just my dad's...
- Hey.
- That friend of Bobby.
He's a drunk as a lumber yak.
He drinks like a fish, yeah,
but not the same stuff.
My feet's pooped just
keeping himself up.
Feets is pooped?
For 18 years I've
tried to teach you
- how to speak good American.
- Yeah, I speak as good
- broken American as you do.
- Lice.
- “Feets is pooped."
- All right then.
My foots is peeped.
(Mike groans)
You're a million
miles away, Ted.
And just when I thought I was
beginning to get through to you.
Look, Dorothy,
I'm out of my element
in a place like this.
(mumbles) This preoccupation
with trivialities.
(Mike imitates his mumbling)
I’m what you might call
a square, I guess.
- Or a dull bastard.
- I’m real, aren't I?
I don't know.
Sometimes I think you are,
and then I see it as
part of (mumbling)
"Sometimes I just trail
off. I don't know..."
That sounds like
a high-class social.
Is that what it is?
(Mike mumbles)
We can expect a shock.
Last night it was
the Jefferson place.
And tonight, maybe here.
Nah, we stay here.
Ah, hobbits.
It's not.
The cook says it comes
out of the ocean.
It's tall, tall like a building,
and it has got arms
like a pile-driver.
I am not afraid.
For 18 years I'm married to you.
Nothing scares me anymore.
"I'm a stupid square-head."
(Crow belches)
I want to know why you
had to import a hypnotist.
Why don't you get him to
perform for us, darling?
I don't use hypnotism
to amuse drunks.
"I use it to get women."
No, Bob.
Why don't you go and
drink yourself up
a nice parade of
pink elephants, huh?
- Last chance, Dorothy.
- “To have me urp on you."
I'll give you one
more chance to marry me.
- Look familiar, Mike?
- Hey, you.
We'll have a
honeymoon for three.
You, me and a whiskey bottle.
The Hazelden holiday party.
(doorbell rings)
Ah, the party can start.
(imitates babbling)
"My poopies is peepee."
- Jeez.
- It’s so thrilling
to have you here, doctor.
Absolutely thrilling.
- My pleasure, madam.
- “Hello."
"Keg in the
bathtub as usual."
"Hit me. I'm locked up."
- Beautiful, isn't she?
- A strange beauty.
- “Weird figures."
- “You're good, too."
I might stay the
night at Lombardi's.
Oh? Evidently she
made quite an impression.
- Didn't she?
- “Only sexually. D'oh."
"Blockbuster Video."
Oh, just a minute please.
"Ow, my elbow."
"Your house is
nicely gift-wrapped."
"We're gonna
rock this place."
Lieutenant James
at the front door.
Oh?
"Go cream some
fish, you square-head."
"INS. You harboring
unfunny Swedes?"
What can I do for you?
I'm very anxious to
catch Dr. Lombardi's act.
Do you mind?
Mind?
No, not at all.
- Hiya, doc.
- Hello, lieutenant.
An excellent idea. Very good.
A nice little touch.
"I'm gonna kick
your ass so bad."
I see Dr. Lombardi's got
himself another follower.
I had him in jail once, but
Chappel's lawyer sprung him.
“But how are you?"
Didn't have enough evidence.
You're going to have to
help me on this one, doc.
It's more in
your line than mine.
You're not falling for
that supernatural hokum?
- Battle of the mumblers.
- I don't really know
what I'm going for.
I know he's a killer.
Lieutenant Mickey Hart.
He doesn't really deny it.
He just laughs at me
and says, "Prove it."
You keep your eyes
peeled, will you, doc?
(Crow imitates their mumbling)
All right folks, curtain
time. Take your seats please.
"Expecting a
little bigger crowd,
"but I guess we
should start then."
Man, their stage presence.
He's the Sammy Davis
Jr. of hypnotists.
"Okay, couple
of announcements.
"The bathrooms are
there and there."
(Mike sings fanfare)
Ladies and gentlemen.
It has been my good fortune
to find in this young lady
the perfect hypnotic subject.
Through her I will reveal to you
some of the hidden
mysteries of life itself.
"First we need
a location, okay?"
Look at me, Andrea.
- “Huh, that's amazing!"
- Are you ready?
Yes.
I shall touch you, and
soon you will be asleep.
"So, like every night."
"You okay, honey?
You feel all right?
"You're a little warm."
Good.
Now, you can hear
everything I say.
"Yes, I am beer
ever-limping you day."
Raise your right arm, please?
"Which way to the
bar, Andrea? Har-har."
Lower it.
Now the left arm, please.
Starts kind of slow and
then fizzles out altogether.
Put it down please.
"Now for the finale,
both of them! Thank you!"
Now take your
place by the couch.
"How much is six
take-away four, Andrea?
"Good."
A little forward,
please, Andrea.
Yeah, it's their German
expressionist home-life.
Now sit down on the couch.
Could they have
skipped a bit? (sighs)
(loudly) Sit down, Andrea.
She's trying
to fight him off.
"It's a big slab
of sit down for you."
"Thank you, ladies
and gentlemen."
We are privileged
to have with us tonight
one of the country's leading
exponents of psychic research.
"B. Torgersen."
- Dr. Erickson.
- “Take the gum out, please."
Since Dr. Erickson
has called me
a fraud and a charlatan,
I invite him to join
me on this platform
- so that he may expose me.
- No, eww.
So that he may
show you why and how
I perpetrate a fraud.
(Servo laughs maniacally)
If you please, doctor.
If you don't
mind, I'll sit here
with the paying customers.
"Fascinating, captain."
Do you refuse, doctor?
Go on, Ted, get up
there and show him up.
"Ted! Ted! Ted! Ted!"
Really, Ted, you should.
♪ Via con dios
Please Ted, you've got to.
Wow, this is just
like Courtney Cox
in that Springsteen video.
"All homosexuals
to the stage, please.
"Ha, I'm kidding."
My next experiment is a
most interesting one, doctor.
I shall prove that life
is an endless chain.
That we are given the gift of it
not for one lifespan but
since the beginning of time.
Wow, he's got
a Jiffy Pop head.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
- “Lick me."
I shall give you living
proof of reincarnation.
Of perpetual life itself.
(light music)
(Observer cries)
My entire world is destroyed.
Everything I knew and
held dear is gone.
(flatly) Oh, uh-huh?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Mike Nelson destroyed
my planet too.
Monster.
Hey, hand me the
Cheez-Its, will ya?
And don't forget,
you got to pony up
some gas money too,
got that, powder?
(Pearl and Bobo laugh)
Hey, I know what
let's do, let's sing.
Let's sing a round of
Row, Row, Row Your Boat.
Okay, I'll start.
♪ Row, row, row your boat
♪ Gently down the
(Observer sobs)
No, no. Wait a second.
You start when I
point at you, okay?
♪ Row, row, row your boat
♪ Gently down the stream
No, no, no, no.
- No, no, no.
- What?
You start at the
beginning of the song.
It's a round, dammit, a round.
- Now sing!
- (stressed) Okay.
♪ Row, row, row your boat
♪ Gently down the stream
(Bobo starts to sing)
♪ Merrily, merrily
♪ Michael row the boat ashore
(Pearl shouts and Observe sobs)
You know what?
I'm glad you're the last
of your civilization.
Oh, Lawgiver.
(pop and hiss)
Oh, and now we have a flat.
Oh, it doesn't make
any difference, Bobo.
Well we can't
ride the whole way
on the rim now, can we?
We're in space. It
doesn't make any difference.
Women.
Jeez, I'll get out and fix it.
(Bobo screams)
Oh, my.
By the way, Mike Nelspants,
this doesn't mean
that you won't not
be finishing your movie, mm-mm.
In fact, quite the opposite.
It means that you won't not
be not finishing your movie.
No way.
(Observer sobs)
Right, Brain Guy?
Oh, yes.
No.
Whatever. I don't know.
(thud)
Hey, nice place.
Well, I'd better
go get that ape
before he gets hair
all over that planet.
I'm sorry, were
you talking to us?
In the basket. Win a quarter.
(buzzer)
- Oh, we've got movie sign.
- Movie sign.
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
Little different from
up here, eh college boy?
This might not
be the moneymaking
extravaganza they
thought it would be.
"Do you think I'm Dale?"
"You're with me while
you (shouts) sleep."
Very deep.
There's an unkillable
funk from his tuxedo.
Your eyes are
getting heavy, Andrea.
"So's your bottom,
I've noticed."
You cannot open them.
"I put superglue
in your mascara."
"I had smoky Gouda
cheese today. You smell it?"
Will you examine her, doctor?
"For free, yeah."
(quietly) "Tell a joke
or something. Juggle."
She is under
hypnosis. Go ahead.
Very thorough examination.
Now you are traveling
back through time and space.
"And flavor."
Farther.
Farther back.
"You've canceled the paper.
You've stopped the milk."
(dreamy music)
Come forward.
- Come forward, quickly.
- “Make up your mind."
(flatly) "We're having fun."
That's better.
(whispers)
"Would you lie down?
"You forgot to wear a slip."
Now stop when you want to.
Stop when you see
something familiar.
- You want to stop now?
- “Yeah."
Where are you?
"Looking live and
sold-out Giants Stadium."
(cockney accent) In the
Yeoman Oxton Road in London.
What is your name?
Elizabeth Ann Wetherby.
"My father is principal
of Riverdale High."
You're smiling, Elizabeth.
"No, it's just gas."
Is something
pleasant taking place?
I've brought Captain Earnest
Blystone to see me father.
He is going to ask for
me 'and in marriage.
(mumbling) "What the
hell is that all..."
Dr. Erickson is
going to question you.
You will answer him.
"It will be multiple
choice and a few
"short essay questions."
"There. (whispers) Erickson,
better start the car."
(quietly) "Sleep."
Oh, great act. Man,
you are eating it raw.
"My first question,
will I get the part
in This Island Earth?"
What year is it, Andrea?
- “The year of the cat."
- 1618.
The year of our Lord.
"In 'Ertford,
'Ereford and 'Ampshire."
Who is the reigning monarch?
James Stewart.
(as Jimmy Stewart)
"Now, wait a second.
"You're crazy and you're
driving me crazy too."
Who is Lord
Chamberlain of his court?
The Earl of Somerset.
What's his
wife's maiden name?
Francis 'Oward.
"No, wait, Susan Lankowski.
"Damn, that's not it either."
You will no doubt
authenticate this information.
I will.
"You must admit, this
would be impossible to fake."
"Your witness, counselor."
Now we are moving
forward in time.
"It's the year kajillion."
You are older. Much older.
"You qualify for
senior discounts."
You're in your last
illness, Elizabeth.
- You're on your deathbed.
- Smells like it too.
Me son David is at me side.
"Gone."
He said he would do as I ask.
- Now he sits and waits.
- “So do we."
- “Boo!"
- What did you ask of him?
"We got to sit
here for this crap?"
That I be buried in
Ceries Brook near me husband.
And that Earnest's medallion
be buried with my...
"Smell my mustache."
What does that
medallion look like?
- It is a gold shield.
- A geld shaled?
With one ruby set in it.
Is there an
inscription on it?
"Because I lost
one like that."
Yes.
"It says, 'I
am a diabetic.' "
"To me loyal subject."
It says "Me loyal subject?"
Earnest Blystone.
It is engraved with
King Charles's seal.
"What the hell did she say?"
"No, I can't hear a thing.
Can you hear anything?"
"Yeah, jumpin'
jiminy, I know."
Thank you, Elizabeth.
"Why don't you
punch out now?"
That is enough.
You will rest now. Sleep.
Deep sleep.
"Big pans of sloppy sleep."
More.
Deeper.
"Ah, Lombardi, you got
me parked in out there."
You're putting her
in a cataleptic state.
That's dangerous.
She's survived
the danger before.
Excuse me please.
"I knew we should have
hired Williams and Ree."
Where are you now, Elizabeth?
"Under a big cloud
of your halitosis."
(bad cockney
accent) In space.
- Floating in space.
- Like oregano?
Are you alone?
There are many
others with me.
"They all say, 'Back off.' "
Can I summon you
out of the spirit world
- to be with me?
- You can summon me.
I will come.
(Crow sighs)
I call you.
You know, I would actually
welcome a drum
solo at this point.
(Servo coughs)
"Oh boy, look at the time.
"Gotta go."
Ooh, wow, her
catalytic converter's out.
I can see you, but I
don't believe the others can.
Oh, how convenient.
Those who believe can see.
Her accent's all
over the British Isles.
I see her.
I do see her.
Too much duviner.
Make your physical
presence known
to those who believe only
what their eyes can see.
Ooh, try diagramming
that sentence.
Open a window.
(music intensifies)
That one.
Kurt Waldheim is
finally discovered.
"Now run to the corner
and get me a pack of smokes."
Now come back
here, Elizabeth.
"Don't you leave
until you finish
"your homework, young lady."
Wow, saw Leo Kottke once,
and he was more exciting.
(gasps) That couldn't have
been done by a pull cord.
His act got an A+ from
Entertainment Weekly.
"I ate the whole cheese tray.
"I'm really sorry everyone."
Lombardi's act just
keeps on giving, doesn't it?
Yeah, he's the James
Brown of hypnosis.
King, come here.
No, no, leave him.
"Do I have
something in my teeth?"
- I’ll control him.
- “I have the remote."
"You will think
about Snausages."
"The part of Carlo
Lombardi will be played by
"a lump of melted wax."
"I'm in a call to the
Bishop of Salisbury."
Will you take him
away please, Elizabeth?
Oh King, you tried
hard in this movie.
You just didn't have
anyone to work with.
(people murmur)
There aren't
many who can control
an animal by hypnosis,
are there, doctor?
No.
He did what I told him
without a single word.
That's because he's a dog.
You may return, Elizabeth.
"Andy."
Why do you hesitate?
"Did you step in King poop?"
What?
"I told you to
go before we left."
At this moment?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I regret to say
that the creature who
has cost so many lives
is on his way here
among us even now.
(people gasp)
"He was seen leaving
"the train station an hour ago."
She gets up to faint.
You better get
some water, quickly.
"Okay, good, we'll
have an intermission then.
"Good. Fine."
What do you
mean? In this house?
I don't know.
But she's in the ocean
now, preparing to come out.
So she's a
scuba-diving lesbian.
- Well, doctor?
- “Get a brewski?"
You're a clever man.
I don't know how you did it,
but it isn't through
science as I understand it.
I have a way of
proving myself to you,
but it's going to be harsh.
"I'm going to tan your
little dimpled bottom.
"Let me get the belt."
"Yeah, I got the
check. Let's blow."
Now you're going back in
time to the very beginning.
"It's a very good
place to start."
By the power that
is mine, I command you.
"All right, I beg you.
Please, pretty please?"
(violin music)
"Do we need new drapes
for our green room?"
"They want more.
They're shouting.
"Holding up cigarette lighters."
"How long has she
had this protrusion?"
Barely has a pulse.
Take her out of this.
- She stays as she is.
- “One-dimensional."
You have no right to
leave her like this.
- I have my own right.
- “And I'm my own grandpa."
If you wish to
try to take her
out of hypnosis, you may do so.
You know I can't do that.
You induced this state.
You must release her.
Then she remains as she is.
"Are you and I okay though?
"I just want to check in."
"All this for a
half-price beer. Man."
(people talk at once)
"The only person who
can save our country
"is Rufus T. Firefly."
Did you see which
way Lombardi went?
Out on the terrace.
You're not going out there.
"You're a woman,
so you deserve
"no answer to your question."
Sir Topham
Hatt's evil brother.
(menacing music)
(gasps) Donald Duck
used the ring of power.
Mandrake the Moron.
"Touchdown!"
"I dreamed I was
married to Jackson Browne!"
"Hmm, nah.
"I just don't have
my heart in it today.
"I've got a bunch
of things to do
"back in the ocean anyway.
"See you."
"Ah, who am I trying to kid?
"I'm not a She Creature,
I'm a She Loser."
Carlo Lombardi,
champion of the caber toss.
"If I could just throw
up, I'd feel better."
Last night topped everything,
and Lombardi and all
that creature talk,
- he had us in a panic.
- He did it deliberately.
He's aiming for
the big circuits.
You don't make
much of him, do you?
I only know he's an
extremely clever man.
- And an evil one.
- “And a smelly one."
I'm glad your dad
asked them to stay over.
I want to try and talk
to that assistant of his.
Professionally?
It's a really
odd split-screen.
He's had her in a complete
hypnotic subjugation.
A virtual slave to his world.
I'm going to try and
break that hold on her.
"What do you think, tree?"
Good morning, Miss Chappel.
Doctor.
I've been thinking of
your work, Dr. Lombardi.
I think it requires
some serious study.
- Oh, good, I'm delighted.
- “In fact I'm radiant."
I want to talk
to your assistant.
Of course. Any time you wish.
- Perhaps this morning.
- Fine.
You set it up for me then.
"Oh, by the way, I
backed up the toilet.
"Sorry about that."
"Cracking good toast
this morning, eh, what?"
You really poured it
on last night, didn't you?
That She Creature stuff was
a stroke of sheer genius.
Everyone let out like the
plague was after them.
They'll be talking it up today.
- Yes, I've no doubt of that.
- Hmm.
And that stuff on the
pier the other night,
the way you tied in with that.
That was a very fortunate
coincidence for us.
- Yes, very.
- By the way, I shall require
more suitable living quarters.
Shall I stay here
'til I find them?
Thank you very much.
(Mike blusters in
English accent)
It's Carlo Kato
Lombardi Kaelin.
Ah, the Exxon Valdez beach.
"Is this felt?
It is now." (laughs)
"Thank you for
meeting me here,
"at the sound stage
by the beach."
What are you doing out here?
"Looking bleary."
Trying to get away from you.
- For a few minutes, anyway.
- Not even for a minute.
"Ever heard of
personal space?"
I'll never be free of you.
Why did it have to be me?
"Uh, 'Sleep?' "
It was meant to be.
"Your earwigs are back."
If you knew how I hated it.
Hated you.
"You're falling in
love with me, aren't you?"
You will do as I say.
"You will not go to the
prom with Tim Hariboth."
Come here.
"Okay, I'm
under your command,
"but do you have
to micromanage me?"
- You're asleep, Andrea.
- “Oh, cut the crap!"
You can hear what I'm saying.
You can understand me.
She used a little too
much false eyelash glue.
- Yeah.
- You're relaxed, Andrea.
I bet he does this whenever
he needs to borrow a
couple of bucks from her.
"I can't hear
you, Mayo-naise."
Dr. Erickson wishes
to talk to you.
"He wants to
level your eyes."
He's going to try
to hypnotize you.
You must resist him.
You will resist him.
"As effectively as
I'm resisting you?"
- He is our enemy.
- “He's a Commie."
He is trying to destroy us.
You understand?
"He's jealous of
our dynamite roadshow."
Beauty like yours
must not be destroyed.
It belongs to me.
Is he attempting a
docking procedure here?
I love you, Andrea.
(Servo winces)
And you love me too.
(Mike groans)
He has the raw sex
appeal of Caspar Weinberger.
Say it.
(Mike groans)
No!
She should get a Purple
Heart for doing this role.
I hate you with all my heart.
"Really? Then
we're to be married."
I could make your
grovel in the dirt.
I can turn you into
Elizabeth Wetherby.
"Or Weather Elizabethby."
But I can't make you love me.
Someday going to kill you.
- I should kill you.
- “No, I should kill you."
But the artist is vain.
You mean Jeff Koons?
He can't destroy the
beauty he's created.
"Oh, I'm standing
on you. I'm sorry."
"Well, he is kind of cute."
♪ I don't know how to love him
Hiya, doc.
"Look, my mouse melted."
Oh, hello. Come in.
"Look, I'm a scientist."
Lombardi tells me
he's coming here today.
He's agreed to
conduct a demonstration
- under clinical conditions.
- Mind if I sit in?
No.
I'd like to set-up
a tape recorder.
"Nope, doing science."
Understand me, doc.
The man is a killer
and I can't touch him.
♪ Can't touch this
(Servo hums)
Statement like that
calls for some proof.
I've got none.
All I know is he hates the
world and everybody in it.
"With no food, gerbils died."
- Man kills for love, or...
- “That other thing."
Hate, or profit.
Where do these killings fit in?
All three, and don't
forget the profit angle.
Lombardi has become
quite a national figure.
I don't know if
he's responsible
for those murders or not.
But I do know he's a
very dangerous man.
"And he makes a
great breakfast."
Dave Berg, scientist.
"Wah, haven't you left yet?"
You've lumped
them all together.
Hypnotism, spiritualism,
age regression.
Reincarnation and
soul transmigration.
(sings) Soul!
Transmigration!
We all have a secret
willingness to believe in
some of the things
he's offering.
Green Stamps.
The passing of the soul
into another body after death.
That life is eternal.
That we can communicate
with the dead.
"Snow blowers that talk?"
Lombardi fancies
himself the miracle man
who's been granted the power
to prove these things right.
He's an egomaniac
playing god.
He claims that the life
process is continuous,
that he can take it back
to a former existence
and not only communicate
with it, but cause it...
- “Uh, line?"
- To materialize.
- Yeah.
- To become a physical thing.
- “Can you stand it?"
- According to Lombardi,
the She Creature was
the primitive life body
of somebody living today.
"It was the strawberries."
What do you make of that?
We're still searching
for the answer.
"We found the answer.
"The answer is her dress."
Some of the details
she's given previously
have been proven
remarkably accurate.
That was the medallion
that was given
to her husband by King Charles.
"What? Am I in
this scene? What?"
It was found in a
grave near Ceries Brook.
The headstone read,
"Elizabeth Wetherby Blystone,
"1600 to 1651."
Then it was planted there.
- Oh, this is preposterous.
- “For the love of Pete."
Do you hold with
this nonsense, Erickson?
My mind is open.
"As is my fly. Thank you!"
Go on with your
experiment, Mr. Lombardi.
"Hi."
- Uh, Dr. Lombardi.
- Of course.
"Mr. Lombardi."
You know, it's quite
simple, gentlemen,
to disbelieve
anything that shatters
your smug concepts.
"Yeah, stick it to the man!"
I'm taking this girl
back to a time in her life
- over 300 years ago.
- “To caveman times."
Perhaps I can take her
back farther than that.
Hey, Bunsen Honeydew.
To the time of the Pharaohs.
(Crow hums cartoon
Pharaoh music)
Even to the beginning
of creation itself.
"Don't act, don't act."
One soul, traveling
the entire distance.
- Utter nonsense.
- “Thank you."
I can materialize her
in any one of her lives.
Let's just get her
going in this one.
I can transport her
from what she is...
"To what she is."
To what she was.
"Oh, bull cookies."
Really, lieutenant, are
we supposed to watch this?
This is penny arcade drama.
Doctor, have I ever
been alone in this room?
"Not while I was here."
(light music)
"Hi honey, you there?"
I'm talking to
you, Elizabeth.
"But I'm not touching
you. Does this bug you?"
You're going
into a deep sleep.
Huh, big surprise.
Very deep.
"Imagine you don't
have a mustache."
He's so expressive.
She's not responding.
"We need jumper cables."
Someone in this room is
fighting me for her will.
"And you'll stay after
until I find out who."
Is it you, doctor?
(mutters) Yes, I'm sorry.
"I thought it was someone
else's will. I'm sorry."
- A deep sleep, Elizabeth.
- “Chicago style."
- Very deep.
- “Very Chicago style."
That's better.
(dreamy music)
You are now suspended
in time and space.
"A dimension not of sight
and sound but of mind."
Now I'm going to
give you a substance.
"In my zapper boots."
Not form, but substance.
"You are in a thick sauce."
You will take back the
soul that once was yours.
"And take back all
my empty beer bottles."
Andrea will give it to you.
"Yes, I snuck a peek
at you. I'm sorry."
Now, put...
You can express
yourself in movement.
(despairingly) No, not
interpretive dance, no.
No.
He boldly plays a
guy who stands there.
(cascading music)
It's just menthol action,
folks, don't worry.
"Who-o-o let one?
"Ugh."
"Oh dear, oh cripes."
Would you take Professor
Anderson's glasses off please?
"Well, this is
highly irregular.
"Whoa, wow, wow, whoa."
Put them back on.
Or, just reverse the film.
That is enough, Elizabeth.
- I think we've convinced them.
- Ah yeah, they're convinced.
Would you return Andrea's
soul to her, please?
Thank you.
She's got visible,
something, line.
Those who believe
can actually see
the process of transmigration.
- I saw nothing.
- Nor I.
- Trickery.
- “Dickery dock."
Very clever, Dr. Lombardi.
But absolutely meaningless.
"Come on, I worked
really hard on that."
You can't see because
you don't wish to see.
"Just wait out
the scene, Lance."
I thought I wanted
recognition from you,
but now I see it
means nothing to me.
"I'm gonna take
my soul and go home."
Now you will awaken.
You will feel refreshed, Andrea.
"Like a country lane
after a spring shower."
You will open your eyes.
"Get a Juice Box and have
someone drive you home."
And so our story ends.
You said before you were
giving her substance
but not form.
- What did you mean by that?
- “Nothing. I..."
I could have bought
her to you in the flesh.
Just as she was 300 years ago.
Come now, doctor. We're
too old for fairy-tales.
"Not me!"
Do you seriously
expect men of science to--
I expect nothing.
I want nothing.
"Well, maybe a back
rub or some fudge,
- “but other than that."
- Come, Andrea.
Yup, she's refreshed.
Up and at 'em.
Just leaping out of bed.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
"Sorry about fighting
for her will here.
"I don't know what I was..."
What do you make it of it?
"I'm trying to
remain neutral.
"Could you not
ask me questions?"
- I don't know.
- “Lance, cool down, man."
This belongs to
the police department.
I'd better take it along.
"Yextri, yextri, those
scientifically-disproven
"Elizabeth Wetherby is real."
"Jake Gittes nostril
slash at reservoir."
"Theft of Dodgers continues."
Well, grips the interest
of one disturbed editor.
Why dontcha just put 'em
right in the discount bin there?
"Some hate him. Others
merely loathe him."
This is a
warehouse for returns.
Book's passed the
million sales mark.
"I wish yours would sell."
"Your roasted
elephant garlic, sir."
Thank you, Oliver.
I have closed a deal
with the Beale syndicate.
395 newspapers are starting
to serialize the Wetherby
for the next month.
How's that for a quick
profit, Lombardi?
You're a genius, Mr. Chappel.
Huh? Oh, I am.
"Except for that
rummy Punjab bullet."
Well, now that
you're in the big chips
you'll be able to find
yourself somewhere to stay.
"What-what? Fried
fin? Willy-wag? What?"
Get yourself something
big, something nice.
- You can afford it.
- No, I'll stay right here.
If I decide to move,
I'll let you know.
"But perhaps you could
stay out of my bed."
King? King?
Where's King? I haven't seen
him since early this morning.
I hardly see him since Dr.
Lombardi took over this place.
Unfortunately, Miss
Chappel, your dog and I
- are not compatible.
- “I hollowed him out
"and made a fruit
bowl out of him.
"I hope that was all right."
"Lombardi warns
of more killings."
(French accent)
"Oui, I did that thing."
Don't press your luck, doc.
Lay off the predictions
for a while.
One miss and our
profits nosedive.
I'm certain our good
fortune will continue.
- Hmm.
- “Yes."
Van Cliburn's Express.
No, it's Von Ryan's Express.
Oh.
"Eggs, butter, cereal,
milk, toilet paper."
And it's "Van Cliburn," so...
- Oh, jeez.
- Yeah.
"You will applaud
feeling refreshed."
"I'm so sorry. I'll
refund all of your money."
"And soon they're
opening for Senor Wences."
"Thanks for teleporting
in for this scene, honey."
(harassing music)
(Servo imitates train to music)
"Crowds of up to
six applauded wildly."
- “Get him!"
"And they climbed up a radio
tower, and did their act."
World's narrowest car.
Yeah, this should
clear everything up.
Carlo Lombardi
is Deep Throat.
Sorry I've made it so
difficult for you to follow me.
What were you
doing down there?
- Oh, communing with nature.
- “Okay, I was tinkling."
But now I feel the
need of human company.
- “Know anyone?"
- Shall we walk to my house?
I need to
re-grease my person.
Well, we've come
full something.
"I've got some more info
on the movie you may need."
And then without
warning, a kissing spree.
Worf, what are you up to?
(woman screams)
"I have to be home by 11."
Don't worry, they have AAA.
(shouts) "We're okay!"
So, there's a cliff a
couple of feet away, huh?
The topography of this
movie is getting suspicious.
"Well, we might have
to rock it a little."
"I hope they stop screaming.
"It's getting really annoying."
I was walking with Lombardi
when I heard the scream.
But I knew he did it.
He's a murderer.
And I can't touch him.
♪ Can't touch this
(Mike hums tune)
"Audience ready
to kill selves."
Hey, my band's coming
over to practice. That okay?
That thing last
night, I didn't like it.
Unfortunate.
Such a nice couple.
I feel as though
I killed them myself.
You? Push a car over a cliff?
Well, hardly.
"Oh, and I ate your
last Hot Pocket. Sorry."
There are two bank books.
One in your name,
one in Dorothy's.
- Who's Dorothy?
- Oh yes, her dowry.
You will see that
each holds a deposit
- of $250,000.
- Well, we've done
- amazingly well.
- Hmm.
We've only just started.
That should keep you in style.
- Somewhere else.
- Ouch.
I want you to
move out of here.
- “Yes, yes."
- No, it's better
- that I stay.
- “It's over, Carl."
Hmm.
Hmm-hmm.
Oh, no, you can't stare me down.
I can look right back at you.
And I'll tell you what I see.
I see a dirty sideshow
fortune teller
with delusions of grandeur.
You're very foolish to
say those things to me.
- You're an ignorant man.
- “Well, I try to keep busy.
"Hey."
I assume our business
relations are over.
What for?
I'm onto a good thing.
We'll continue our business
affairs at my office.
This was the
prequel to Jeffrey.
I'll move out tomorrow.
Ah, he's moving.
I understand you've
invited some people
here tonight for
a demonstration.
Tomorrow will suit me fine.
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
Hey, that's our hero
from the movie today.
Lance Fuller.
Oh yeah, this is his
legendary book, Do Not Act.
I'm studying his
non-acting method.
Hey, I was wondering
if you could
help me out with a
couple of scenes.
- I’ve got King Lear here.
- Sure.
Yeah I've head the Fuller
method is perfect for the Bard.
Yeah.
Okay, so I'm
- the Duke of Albany then.
- Right, right.
Okay.
All friends shall taste
the wages of their virtue
and all foes the cup
of their deservings.
Oh see, oh see.
(flatly) My poor fool hanged?
No, no, life? (mumbles quietly)
Why should a horse, a
dog, a rat, have life?
And now none at all?
Ah, a little too
much eye contact, Mike.
Listen to Lance here.
"Do not under any
circumstances listen
"to your fellow actor.
"Simply wait 'til
they've stopped talking."
Yeah, I think I
wasn't looking down
- at the floor enough.
- Yeah.
I think that's what it was.
Let's try a scene
from The Odd Couple.
This time remember
what Lance says here.
"At most, a mild and
petulant show of incredulity
"whatever the circumstances
of the scene."
- Got it.
- Okay, this should be fun.
I'm Felix. Here we go.
It's not spaghetti.
It's linguine. Linguine.
(mumbling) Now it's garbage.
No, just a little
too much emotion.
Okay, all right,
I think I got it.
(monotone) I'm as mad as hell,
and I'm not gonna
take it anymore.
Not quite. A
little flatter, Mike.
- How about Schindler's List?
- Okay, all right.
(flatly) I could
have done more.
Could have saved more people.
Okay, okay, you've
almost got it there.
Okay, now try the
scene from Waterworld.
Now you're Kevin Costner, you
see your precious catamaran
- sinking into the ocean.
- Right into the ocean!
And, go.
(nothing) My boat.
- Perfect! That's it!
- Yeah!
- Wonderful!
- Money, baby!
Think I got it?
Thanks a lot for helping.
We'll be right back.
I was looking for
a moment there,
and I think I found that moment.
(light music)
Poor guy.
You were expecting
someone else, huh?
"Maybe that cipher
of a scientist?"
Dr. Erickson, perhaps?
"Know if he's
looking for a roommate?"
Well, no matter.
Did he get that suit
at Petite Sophisticate?
We're leaving the
country tomorrow, you and I.
"Bring your past lives."
I'm not going with you.
"Man, completely
out of nowhere."
I love him.
You'll be with
me on the plane.
"And I get your peanuts."
- You will do as I say.
- “And I say clog dancing."
I have found the
power to resist you.
"It accidentally rolled
under my seat cushion."
He has given it to me.
"But I have to give
it back next semester."
"Hi."
No one can take you from me.
I live only for you.
You're the light that
shines out of the darkness.
"You're like my fish locator.
"You're like my global
positioning system."
"One crappy day I'm having.
"Lost my boyfriend,
lost my girlfriend.
"Got kicked out
of my apartment."
He will never have you.
"Look into my
upsetting mustache."
I'll kill him.
"You'd do that for me"?
"I'm sorry, what
were you saying?"
"Look deep into my eyebags."
You'll kill him.
"Come on, come
on. You want some?
"What you got, huh? Huh?
"I'm taking you down."
This time you
will do as I say.
"Viewers are invited to
finish the scene themselves."
I haven't seen
you and Dorothy
together much lately.
What's the matter?
Lovers' quarrel?
"You haven't heard.
I'm not in this movie."
Well, here's something that
will help you patch it up.
"Arnold Stang's autograph.
Should fetch a pretty penny."
- $250,000. Dorothy's.
- And yours.
You helped to set it up.
There's more coming in.
Go over and show it to her.
She doesn't know
anything about it.
This'll help you to forget
Carlo's little girl, eh?
Hmm.
I don't think I could forget
where the money came from.
I told you I was a
fool about such things.
I'm sure I'll never
have another offer
like that again, but thanks
for giving me the first offer.
Hey, he's moving,
look at that.
The scene was
actually blocked.
- Hi, Ted.
- “Hi, little fella."
Who are you looking for?
Andrea Elizabeth or
Elizabeth Andrea?
I saw both of her down
near the ocean a while ago.
Thanks.
Ted.
What's she got that I haven't?
(Servo mimes vomiting)
Money? Breeding?
Social position?
"Don't answer. It's a trap."
Some people have
too much of everything.
You don't have
enough of anything.
Guess I had that coming.
She's a nice girl, Ted.
"Well, it was
nice meeting you."
"Thanks for the Bob
Dole handshake, jerk."
(slow music)
Here comes Marty
Markham to the rescue.
- Hi, beautiful.
- Bob.
- “Hi, fallback."
- What are you drinking?
That's a scotch,
bourbon, gin cocktail.
No vodka?
You must be tapering off.
Let me know when you get down
to the scotch and
bourbon cocktails.
It's neat that she's
interested in his hobby.
There goes the gin.
Now I'm down to a bourbon
and scotch cocktail.
And the hydrangea bushes
die a horrible death.
Some squirrels down there
are going to have
a kick-ass party.
"This means you're
cured of alcoholism
"and you'll never have any
bouts of booze drinking again."
"Sessions presents
Summer Gold."
"Gee, I'm supposed to do
"a kids' birthday party
around here somewhere."
You taught me
how to fight him.
- His power is gone.
- “Really?
"When did I do that?"
We'd better be getting
back to the house.
He'll be looking for you.
I don't want to go
through with it tonight.
"Kissing me is
hard, I know, but..."
You've got to.
Resist him publicly and
he'll leave you alone.
"Or bury a toad at
midnight. I don't know."
What if I don’t?
"I'll retain my
football-shaped head."
I'll fight him for you.
"Uh, no, wait, I
won't. Forget it."
I think I'll win.
"By the way, do you know
why we love each other?
"I don't..."
Just stay here a
little longer with me.
"Umm, okay, how's this?"
"Jeez, I lost my
doves too. What next?"
"Did you bring the Frisbee?"
(menacing music)
"Hey, can you pull
my stitches out, bud?"
(dog barks)
- You can kill him.
- “What?"
- I command you.
- “Huh?"
"Yes, King, I will kill him."
"But you didn't
even throw a stick."
(dramatic music)
"Manics!"
(fierce barking)
"Well, good luck."
"It's not me growling.
They dubbed it in."
(flatly) "Ah,
I'm a pirate. Ah."
Get away. He's going crazy.
"His prices are way too low."
"Just had Novocaine."
Get away.
(growling)
"Sorry I lashed out at you
"with the thing."
(dog whimpers)
"I don't wanna be in movies.
"I just wanna eat bacon
strips and chase cars."
"That had no effect on me."
That voice
didn't come from me.
(very deep) "Yes it did."
Let's get away from here.
"Let's stand
over there. Better."
"We're ready to
start, if you'll just,
"if you could sit."
Hey, can I see you a minute?
"I think I killed
that Swedish guy."
I've formed a
few theories by now
and I want to try
them out on you.
- “Santa is the killer.”
- I’m listening.
Every time this
thing has struck,
it's been after one of
these demonstrations.
- “See?"
- That's been the pattern.
- I checked it.
- You think he has
some way of signaling
to his accomplices?
- “I can hear you."
- If you can call them that.
- Another thing I've discovered.
- “I’m part woman."
Every time we find
the footprints coming
out of the ocean, they go back,
exactly the same spot.
You're going
on the assumption
that Lombardi's creature
is the real thing.
It's the only
thing I can go on.
Otherwise it's the
psychopathic ward for me.
Hey, Chet Baker,
security guard.
I'm not sure.
What do you think?
As a scientist I'm
hysterical with laughter.
As a man out for
a social evening,
I'm not so sure.
In fact, very unsure.
All right, folks. Showtime.
House lights out, please.
Hey, send Olaf
out here, will you?
Sure.
"Hey, Fanny and
Alexander, listen up."
Lieutenant James
wants to speak to you.
- Oh.
- Out on the terrace.
Yes, sir.
"I'm making Hellraiser."
Am I under arrest, I hope?
I sure would like to get
away from this spook shop.
Hey, have you
got a tape recorder?
In Mr. Chappel's study.
Can you take me there without
going through the living room?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Come right this way.
That was my favorite
scene in the whole movie.
Right here, sir.
Thank you.
Two giants of
the film industry
finally have a scene together.
"Ladies and
gentlemen, Stomp."
I will touch you gently.
And you will fall
into a deep sleep.
"You have a little
chicken gravy up there."
Your eyes are getting heavy.
"Always criticize my weight."
They're starting
to close now.
"Sorry. You're on your own."
"Ooh, who jiffed
in here? Oof."
So he's backfired.
"He's right.
I'm dying up here."
I will count to four.
And you will fall into
a deep, deep sleep.
One.
Two.
39.
Three.
Four.
"Ha-ha-ha, my
will is in my purse
"and you can't have it."
"Umm, she's
hypnotized. Thank you!"
Ladies and gentlemen, my
subject is not herself tonight.
- She's is too tense.
- “She's a tepee
- and a wigwam."
- Woo!
(Mike and Servo laugh)
(pleadingly)
"Come on, sleep."
Will you take your
place on the couch, please?
"No, you sleep on
the couch tonight."
They should do a
jump ball for her soul.
What exactly is
their act again?
"Dumb, stupid
audience. Jeez."
- Eww.
- You have eyes
- only for mine.
- Don't.
You have ears
only for my voice.
"Nose only for my scent."
Now you're going
into a deep sleep.
- Your eyes are heavy.
- “Uh-huh."
Close your eyes and
go into a deep sleep.
"Like when you're on a
date with Lance Fuller."
Deeper.
- Deeper.
- “Come on. I call."
"Maybe if we did the wave."
She's dead.
(Mike and Crow laugh)
Said before you were
giving her substance,
but not form.
What did you mean by that?
"I don't like this
new Prince album."
I could have brought
her to you in the flesh.
Just as she was 300 years ago.
(stops playback)
"That's all the evidence
"I need, whatever it was."
I'm talking to
you, Elizabeth.
"Elizabeth Ann She Creature."
Where were you born?
He's doing all his old stuff.
"Man, I am taking the
pipe so bad right now."
My subject is disturbed
tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
Her world is disturbed.
I feel a menace to the
people in this house.
I urge you all to
leave here at once.
(murmuring)
Do as he says everybody.
Let's clear out of here.
"But be sure to
tip your waitresses
"and drive carefully
on the way home.
"Goodnight!"
No one's forced
me out of my home.
"Is anybody listening to me?"
"So, you want to end
this movie or something?"
Get her out of it.
Perhaps you can.
Whoa!
You kill me and you kill her.
"You kill her, you
kill Anson Williams."
(light music)
(tense music)
This is probably best.
He couldn't outrun
it or anything.
(gunshots)
No.
"Damn, these seaweed
bullets aren't working."
(gunshot)
"Sea creature
with kung fu grip."
"Assistant
director, anybody know
"when I'm supposed
to do key grip?
"Hello?"
The Creature roughhouses
people to death.
"I was an hour
away from retirement."
"Nothing, nothing.
Project nothing."
(Servo imitates musical notes)
"Tell Moondoggie I love him."
They'll be coming
back this way.
"Maybe not today, maybe
not tomorrow, but..."
- Lombardi was right.
- “Winning isn't everything."
- He did it.
- Did what?
Brought the girl back.
The girl?
"Yeah. Anyway, you
cops ever find my bike?"
"Umm, I'm not quite dead.
"You might want to
get me some help."
(dramatic music)
They tried to light
this, but this movie
is like a super-absorbing
black hole.
- “What? Hello?"
- “Hello?"
- “Can you?"
- “Anybody?"
"I can't see. Ow,
you stepped on my foot."
- “Ow, hey."
- “That's my elbow."
"Tripped."
"And there's the kickoff."
What? How could
they miss each other?
Space has warped
and time is bendable.
The creature was wearing
cleats and toe socks.
Chief, you stay here
with me. We aren't moving.
The rest of you, get
some brush and driftwood.
Anything that'll burn.
What are you
going to do with her?
- What the?
- Put a circle around
all those prints.
Whatever killed
him will be back,
and we'll set fire to it.
Bring back some gas
from the car will you?
That logic is
completely pregnable.
(dramatic music)
He's doing a Noel
Coward play all by himself.
(gasps) The Phillie Phanatic!
(gunshot)
(Crow laughs)
"Say, I hit your
cat. I'm real sorry."
This guy does not
have good escapability.
"Right then, do come
into the house for a sherry.
"We'll have a little chinwag."
Meanwhile, in a
nearby wedding cake.
"I want those
Glengarry leads."
General Tom Thumb.
Wait a minute,
how did he get?
- Foul.
- Illegal procedure.
Looks like my grandma
framed this shot.
Plenty of wall.
(Creature grunts)
Now do you believe, doctor?
Kill it!
"No."
"Wait a minute. You're
not Roy Johnson are you?
"I'm supposed to
kill Roy Johnson."
"No. Bad.
"No. No."
"Well, mm, gosh,
I, mm, hmm. Uh."
And now she's just
pretending to be hypnotized
so she doesn't have to help.
"Okay, girlfriend,
I got the Haagen-Dazs.
"Let's dish."
Fear? Elation? What is it?
"And he said he
was going to call
"but then he doesn't call."
Makes you wonder what
the He Creature
would look like, huh?
Despair? Love? Joy? Tell us!
Man, she's got a
prison matron bosom.
Eww, I think the director
had some issues with
his mother or something.
(Servo sobs)
Concern? Passion?
Hunger? What, Lance?
"Ah, she's got a
slight mustache problem."
You know, you can
overcondition your hair.
Ennui? Angst? Apathy? Gas?
Self-delivering cotton candy.
It's the She Vicks
VapoRub Creature.
"Well, cut the
downdraft there.
"Ooh, back, back! I want
to go the other way!
"Damn."
Cold? Jubilant? Headachey?
His emotional memory
is the previous scene.
"Oh, I ate too
much chocolate.
"Oh, oh."
"Do I have
anything on my face?"
You couldn't kill
the man you loved.
"Hair styled by Elmarco."
I mustn't let you die.
Your beauty must live.
"Your average
attractiveness must live on."
I will touch you
and you will awaken.
Young and beautiful.
Freed forever from the past.
Man, he shouldn't
have siphoned motor oil.
What I have done,
no man can ever do.
Take such a lame act so far.
- “And, I'm dead."
- “Thank you."
Ah, it's working perfectly.
(menacing music)
Ah, Frodo's going snorkeling.
There. Fire.
I can't see anything.
Where I'm pointing
at. Hurry up.
"Okay, civilian."
Hey, it does
seem to be helping.
- I don't see anything.
- Fire!
Maybe they should
have a staff meeting
about letting citizens
boss them around.
- You see anything?
- No.
How about you, doc?
Can you still see something?
No.
I was mistaken.
(Servo laughs)
"Who was that lethargic
lunkheaded stranger?"
"I don't know."
"I'm sorry I touched you,
"but you don't have
to become a nun."
- She was here, wasn't she?
- “I smell Tabu."
Yes.
(flatly) "Wow, look at
those worms down there."
He's got a list of
his facial expressions
taped to her back.
She killed Carlo.
He forced her to
come out of the world.
He should go back to her own.
Huh?
There are a lot
of dark corners
we weren't meant to
pry into, I guess.
"Are you saying you
still haven't showered?"
"Uh, are we
moving over here now?
"I'm right here if you need me."
She'll never
be back, will she?
No.
"And you'll never
be back either, right?"
And the Mysterians.
Man, if I ever
wanted to put a movie
into a stump grinder
this is the one.
- Yeah, me too.
- Man.
(rumbling, clicking and beeping)
So guys, what do you make of
that big question mark
at the end of the movie?
Well, I think they
were asking when,
as in, when will
this movie not exist?
Or, maybe it
was a why question,
as in, why did King
George and his parliament
react with such
indifference, nay arrogance,
to the colonists'
longstanding grievances
of taxation without
representation
leading to the Revolution
which led to the United States
which led to California
which led to Hollywood
and the motion picture
industry which led
ultimately to this hard,
bitter little nut of a movie.
It's a good point.
But I think it may have
been a hmm question,
as in, "Hmm? I'm sorry,
I didn't hear you.
"This crappy movie was
sitting on my head."
Hey say, guys,
it just hit me.
We're free to escape!
Since Mike blew up
the Observers' planet.
- I didn't. I mean, I asked--
- Right, and Mrs. Forrester
and the Brain Guy seem to
be tied up looking for Bobo.
- Yeah, let's boogie!
- Woohoo!
Okay, well, here we go.
- To infinity and--
- Shh! Disney. Lawsuit.
- Some other places!
- Yeah.
(engine coughs)
Hmm.
Doesn't seem to be turning over.
I wonder what's going on.
What's going on?
We got it goin' on, that's
what's going on, huh?
How about this guy here, huh?
I say, "Hmm, I sure would hate
"for those eight balls on
the satellite to escape."
This beautiful man
right here says,
"Let me handle it."
He is holding you here
with his mi-i-ind.
You poor dumb schmucks.
How do you like that?
How'd you like to have
this guy on your crew
instead of those
yappy little tin cans
you hang out with?
- This guy is the best.
- Why, thank you Pearl.
Tell you something
else now sonny.
This guy's gunnin' for you.
You blew up this man's wo-o-rld,
as I will continue to remind him
every chance I get.
You whacked his planet, man,
and he is plenty
cheesed, let me tell you.
Yes, you have destroyed
an ancient and proud race.
My people. And let
me tell you that I--
I was talking.
Boy, everything's
about you isn't it?
- I’m very sorry.
- Anyway Nelson.
You're mine. You'll
never escape.
Never!
(Pearl laughs maniacally)
Excuse me, malevolent one,
but hadn't we ought to
go get Professor Bobo?
Hmm. That's a good idea.
Say, could you hand
me the Cheez-Its?
- Why, certainly.
- Thanks.
(loudly) I,
give, the, orders.
Oh.
Hey, we'd better
go find Bobo.
(slow music)
Ow.
My spine.